A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Education, 1975-1997.
Library of Virginia
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 32651), 1975-1985 (bulk 1982-1984)., Extent: 29 cubic feet (29 boxes)
  - Targets, 1983. (Box 26)
  - Taxation, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 26)
  - Television Engineering Program, 1984. (Box 26)
  - Thaver, Charles O., 1983. (Box 26)
  - TIAA / CREF, 1982-1983. (Box 26)
  - Telecommunications, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 26)
  - Tennessee Better Schools Comm., 1983. (Box 27)
  - Theroux - Pacific Institute, 1984. (Box 27)
  - Thomas, Vincent, 1982-1983. (Box 27)
  - Tidewater Future, 1983. (Box 27)
  - Total Action Against Poverty in the Roanoke Valley, 1982-1984. (Box 27)
  - Tort Liability, 1982. (Box 27)
  - Travel, 1985 Jan-June. (Box 27)
  - Travel - Virginia Air, 1985. (Box 27)
  - Travel - Covington Travel, 1982-1985. (Box 27)
  - Travel - Destination Travel, 1984. (Box 27)
  - Travel - Piedmont Air, 1985. (Box 27)
  - Travel - Red Carpet, 1983-1985. (Box 27)
  - Travel - United Airlines, 1984-1985. (Box 27)
  - Travel Services, 1984. (Box 27)
  - Trible, Paul, 1984. (Box 27)
  - Trinkle, James L., 1984. (Box 27)
  - Trinity Espiscopal High School, 1984. (Box 27)
  - Tur-View Presentations, 1983. (Box 27)
  - Union of Black Episcopalians, 1982-1983. (Box 27)
  - UniServe, District M, 1983. (Box 27)
  - University of Richmond, 1982-1983. (Box 27)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1982-1983. (Box 27)
  - United States Dept. of Ariculture, 1984. (Box 27)
  - United Way Campaign, 1982-1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Congress, 1982. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Congress, 1983. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1984 July-Dec. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1984 Jan-June. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1983. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Dept. of Education - Secretary for Intergovernmental and Interagency Affairs, 1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Dept. of the Interior, 1982-1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. International Center for the Performing Arts, 1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senate, 1982-1984. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senate Program, 1983. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senate Program, 1982. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senator Warner, 1984 Oct-Dec. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senator Warner, 1984 Jan-Sept. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senator Warner, 1983 July-Dec. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senator Warner, 1983 Jan-June. (Box 27)
  - U.S. Senator Warner, 1982. (Box 27)
  - Virginia Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Vanderbilt, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Velzy, Richard, 1981. (Box 28)
  - Viette, Andre, 1981-1982. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Academy of Science, 1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Admissions Council on Black Concerns, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions, 1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association for the Gifted, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Museums, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Private Career Schools Publications, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Secondary School Principals, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Association of Student Financial Aid Administrators, 1982-1985. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Bankers Schools, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Beach Rotary Club, 1982. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Business Council, 1982-1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia College Placement Association, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Council for Private Education, 1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Counselors Association, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Economic Developers Association, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Education Association, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Education Association, 1981-1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Education Association - Presentation, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Education Association - Instructional Conference, 1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Episcopal School, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Forum on Education, 1982-1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, 1982-1983. (Box 28)
  - Virginia High School League, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Home for Boys, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Institue for Scientific Research, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Library Association, 1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1982-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Minority Student Career Development Symposium, 1985. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 1983-1984. (Box 28)
  - Virginia Occupational Information Coordination Comm., 1982-1984. (Box 29)
  - Virginia School Board Association, 1981-1983. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Society for Autistic Children, 1982-1983. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Society for Professional Engineers, 1982. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1983-1984. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Vocational Association, 1982-1983. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Water Resources Research Center, 1982-1983. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Wildlife Federation, undated. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Women's Studies, 1981-1982. (Box 29)
  - Virginia Division of War Veteran Claims, 1984. (Box 29)
  - WCVE Channel 23, 1983-1984. (Box 29)
  - Weiner, George, 1982-1983. (Box 29)
  - West Richmond Rotary Club, 1982. (Box 29)
  - West Virginia, 1984. (Box 29)
  - Whitehouse Fellowship Program, 1984. (Box 29)
  - Wilkinson, Robert, Jr., 1975-1985. (Box 29)
  - Wilson, Richard T., III, 1983. (Box 29)
  - Woodbury Forest School, 1982-1984. (Box 29)
  - Woodie, Pam, 1983-1984. (Box 29)
  - Woodstock Rotary Club, 1982. (Box 29)
  - Worsham, Michael, 1983. (Box 29)
  - Writing Program Administrators, 1982-1983. (Box 29)
  - Yawn, Larry, 1983. (Box 29)
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 34742), 1990-1994., Extent: 52 cubic feet (52 boxes)
  These records were created or collected during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994, though some records may pre-date this time frame. During the Wilder Administration, James W. Dyke, Jr., served as Secretary of Education, 1990-1993, and Karen Petersen served as Secretary of Education, 1993-1994.
  - Financial statements, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Workforce Leadership Council, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Workforce Leadership Council, 1994. (Box 1)
  - Virginia Energy Plan, 1991. (Box 1)
  - Activities, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Virginia Tech - Edward Aguiar, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Local Multipoint Distribution Services - James R. Cooke, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Science Museum of Virginia, 1993. (Box 1)
  - VQuest, 1991. (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Information Technology at University of Richmond, 1993 Nov. (Box 1)
  - Extended school year, 1990. (Box 1)
  - TTFEF, 1991. (Box 1)
  - Plan to Improve Educational Oppotunities for All Virginians, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Early retirement, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Optional retirement, 1990. (Box 1)
  - SGA meetings, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Projections - Educational statistics, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind - Hampton, 199. (Box 1)
  - National Educational Goals, 1992. (Box 1)
  - National Educational Goals - Progress Report, 1991. (Box 1)
  - Books for All Virginians, 1990. (Box 1)
  - A.L. Philpott Manufacturing Center, 1993. (Box 1)
  - America 2000, 1991. (Box 1)
  - Anti-terrorism, 1990. (Box 1)
  - General correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
  - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 1)
  - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Mary Washington College - Financial statements, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Dept. of General Services - Review of Virginia Cooperative Extension, 1993. (Box 1)
  - Bradley case, 1985. (Box 2)
  - Girl's education, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Gender in education, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Business Education Partnerships, 1991. (Box 2)
  - Literary Fund - Interest rate subsidies, 1987. (Box 3)
  - Fund construction of school buildings (HJR 108), 1988. (Box 3)
  - Business Education Partnerships, 1990-1992. (Box 3)
  - Nomination of automated manufacturing, 1990. (Box 3)
  - Workforce 2000, 1991. (Box 3)
  - Business Education Advisory Council, 1992-1993. (Box 3)
  - Employee leave policy, 1992. (Box 3)
  - Business Education Partnerships - Related publications, 1988-1992. (Box 3)
  - Business Edcuation Partnerships - James Madison University, Valley of Virginia Partnerships for Education, 1992. (Box 3)
  - Management standards, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Weekly reports, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Executive Institute, 1991. (Box 4)
  - Virginia's Economic Recovery (SJR 433), 1991. (Box 4)
  - Southern Governors' Association - African Heads of State Summit, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Industrial Extension in Virginia, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Mercedes, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Lease justification, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Commission on Educational Opportunity for All Virginians, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Terry, Mary Sue, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Minority procurement, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Recommendations, 1992-1993. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Budget Symposium, 199. (Box 4)
  - Dyke, James W., Jr., 199. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Community College System, 1992. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities, 1990-1993. (Box 4)
  - General correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
  - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 4)
  - Project Streamline, 1991. (Box 5)
  - Commissions and Studies, 1990-1993. (Box 5)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1990-1993. (Box 5)
  - Kenan Project (Virginia Union University), 1990. (Box 6)
  - Clinton Administration, 1993. (Box 6)
  - President Clinton - Proposals, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Points of Light movement, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Poverty Commission, 1993. (Box 6)
  - Poverty Commission, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Urban Poverty and Low Income Standards, 1992-1993. (Box 6)
  - Council on Information Management, 1993. (Box 6)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1992-1993. (Box 7)
  - Workforce Leadership Council, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Plan for Information Technology Resources, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Education, 1990-1993. (Box 7)
  - Board of Education, 1991. (Box 7)
  - Fordice, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Gender Equity, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Ethics Reform, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Summer Economics Institute - E. Angus Powell Endowment, undated. (Box 7)
  - Employee Pay Incentive, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Commission on Educational Opportunity for All Virginians, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
  - Letters of commendation, 1993. (Box 7)
  - General obligation bonds, 1993. (Box 7)
  - Legislative requests, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1991-1992. (Box 7)
  - Education Commission for the States, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
  - Four Year Goals, 1990. (Box 7)
  - Universities, 1992-1993. (Box 7)
  - Performance Measures Pilot Project, 1990-1993. (Box 7)
  - General correspondence, 1989-1991. (Box 7)
  - General correspondence, 1992-1993. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Committee - Workforce 2000 Partnership for Excellence, 1991. (Box 7)
  - Educational Performance Measures, 1989. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Violent Crime Initiative, 1992-1993. (Box 8)
  - Dropouts, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - CHOICE, 1991. (Box 8)
  - Administration, 1991. (Box 8)
  - Superintendents' Study Group, 1991. (Box 8)
  - Literacy, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - Regional efforts, 191. (Box 8)
  - Racial discrimination, 1991. (Box 8)
  - Vocational Education Programs for Nurses (HB 445), 1990. (Box 8)
  - Project Discovery, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Oracle, 1991. (Box 8)
  - Principal preparation, 1991. (Box 8)
  - School nurses, 1992. (Box 8)
  - Minimum local effort, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Internal audit reports, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Four Year Goal plans, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Governor's speeches, 1991. (Box 8)
  - State Library, 1990-1993. (Box 8)
  - State Library Board, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - Poverty Commission, 1992. (Box 8)
  - Urban Policy, 1992. (Box 8)
  - Sexual Assault Hearings, 1992. (Box 8)
  - Teacher salary issues, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - Fort Belvoir, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Highland County, 1990. (Box 8)
  - Working papers, 1990-1993. (Box 8)
  - Education Summit, 1989. (Box 8)
  - Retirement Task Force, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
  - Early retirement, 1991. (Box 9)
  - Early retirement, 1990. (Box 9)
  - Early retirement - Calculations and targets, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
  - Early retirment - Correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
  - Early retirement - Optional faculty, 1990. (Box 9)
  - Early retirement - Optional retirement plan surveys, 1990. (Box 9)
  - Richmond 2000, 1991. (Box 9)
  - Roanoke, 1990-1993. (Box 9)
  - Rockbridge Co., Rockingham Co., and Russell Co., 1990-1993. (Box 9)
  - Commission Studying Alternative Methods of Financing Certain Facilities at State-Supported Colleges and Universities, 1990-1991. (Box 9)
  - Publication Costs, 1990-1991. (Box 10)
  - Publications (Federal and other states), 1990-1993. (Box 10)
  - State of the Commonwealth address, 1989-1992. (Box 11)
  - Workforce Leadership Council, 1993. (Box 11)
  - Budget, 1993. (Box 11)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1993. (Box 11)
  - Acting pay, 1991-1993. (Box 11)
  - Family life education, 1989. (Box 11)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1990. (Box 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1990-1993. (Box 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1993. (Box 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Colleges and Universities, 1993. (Box 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Virginia Community College System, 1993. (Box 11)
  - Legislative Package (1994), 1993. (Box 11)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Management, 1993. (Box 11)
  - English as a Second Language (ESL), 1992. (Box 11)
  - Welfare Reform, 1993. (Box 11)
  - Gov. L. Douglas Wilder's Agenda for Virginia, 1990. (Box 11)
  - Top education accomplishments, 1993. (Box 11)
  - General correspondence, 1989-1992. (Box 11)
  - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 11)
  - General correspondence, 1994 Jan-Mar. (Box 11)
  - Gabon visit, 1991. (Box 12)
  - Education goals review, 1991. (Box 12)
  - Executive Order 49 (90), 1990. (Box 12)
  - Job placement and training, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
  - Secretary of Education correspondence, 1990. (Box 12)
  - Secretary of Education correspondence with the Governor, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
  - Secretary of Education correspondence with the U.S. Dept. of Education, 1989-1990. (Box 12)
  - University of Virginia, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - General, 1989-1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - General, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Closing, 1987-1988. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Planning Issue Study, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - JLARC Study, 1987-1988. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Dept. of Planning and Budget / Staffing at VSLA, 1989. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Service, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Bill of Rights Tour, 1990-1992. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Planning and budget, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - New building site, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Budget and statistics, 1989-1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Court fees, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - State aid to public libraries, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Phillip Morris project, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - State Library recommendations, 1991-1992. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - Records Center, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Virginia State Library and Archives - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 13)
  - Gunston Hall, 1991. (Box 13)
  - Executive Order 1 (88), 1988. (Box 14)
  - State education correspondence, 1989. (Box 14)
  - Literary Fund - General correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
  - Literary Fund - Cashflow method, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Literary Fund - Virginia Public School Authority, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Literacy - General correspondence, 1987-1989. (Box 14)
  - Literacy - Virginia Literacy Initiative, 1988. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1990. (Box 14)
  - Dept. of Education - Vocation Education, 1989-1990. (Box 14)
  - Dept. of Education - Vocational Education Study, 1989. (Box 14)
  - Dept. of Education - Pupil transportation, 19. (Box 14)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1991. (Box 14)
  - National Science Foundation - V-Quest, 1991-1992. (Box 15)
  - Education Summit (Charlottesville, Va.), 1989. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - General, 1993. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1992. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Tech, 1992. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Longwood, 1991-1993. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - George Mason University, 1992-1993. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - University of Virginia, 1992-1993. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Other Education agencies, 1992-1993. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Other, 1993-1994. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - University of Virginia, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - George Mason University, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - James Madison University, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Old Dominion University, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Radford University, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Tech, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - College of William and Mary, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia State Library and Archives, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Community Colleges, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Dept. of Education, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Dept. of Education, Virginia State Library and Archives, and Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1994. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Other institutions (active), 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia (active), 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - University of Virginia (active), 1994. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Virginia Tech (active), 1994. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Pending, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Information Technology: Sole Source - Correspondence, 1991-1994. (Box 16)
  - Grants procedures - Simplification Committee, 1990. (Box 16)
  - Grants procedures - Simplification Committee, 1991. (Box 16)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Factual Report / Response, 1987 June. (Box 17)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Response, 1988 May. (Box 17)
  - Office of Civil Rights - Plan, 1978. (Box 17)
  - Knight Commission, 1991-1992. (Box 17)
  - Commission on Excellence in Education - A Plan for Virginia's Future, 1986. (Box 17)
  - Governor's Commission on Educational Opportunity for all Virginians (First Meeting Briefing Book), 1990. (Box 17)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Development, 1991-1993. (Box 18)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Development - Summary draft legislation, 1992. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Business Education Partnership Program, 1991-1995. (Box 18)
  - VQuest, 1992-1993. (Box 18)
  - Budget - Secretary of Education, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Virginia College Building Authority, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Dept. of Education / Board of Education - Spending, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Printing costs, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Workforce reduction tools, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Smithsonian Air and Space Museum, 1989-1990. (Box 18)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1993. (Box 18)
  - Project Streamline, 1990-1992. (Box 19)
  - Project Discovery, 1989-1991. (Box 19)
  - National Governors Association (NGA), 1989-1990. (Box 19)
  - Museums (Private), 1990-1992. (Box 19)
  - Virginia Education Loan Authority (VELA), 1987-1992. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Education Loan Authority (VELA) and State Education Assistance Authority (SEAA), 1990-1992. (Box 20)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 1991-1992. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Guaranteed Assistance Program, 1990-1993. (Box 20)
  - Special Education, 1986-1993. (Box 20)
  - Budget - Dept. of Education, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Frontier Culture Museum, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - State Library and Archives, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Gunston Hall, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Science Musuem, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Downsizing, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - General, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Budget - Early retirement, 1991. (Box 21)
  - Consolidated salary authorization, 1991-1994. (Box 21)
  - Faculty salaries, 1990-1993. (Box 21)
  - Higher Education Trust Fund, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1990-1991. (Box 21)
  - Education Common of the States, 1985. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - Richmond City, 1990-1992. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - Virginia Beach, 1992. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - Washington Co., 1992. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - Waynesboro, 1989-1990. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - Westmoreland Co., West Point, Winchester, Wise Co., 1989-1992. (Box 21)
  - Public Schools - York Co., 1992. (Box 21)
  - Virginia-Middle East Peace Commission, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Academic year classified appointments, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Colleges - President bonuses, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Substance abuse, 1990-1992. (Box 22)
  - Workforce Development (HJR 600), 1992. (Box 22)
  - Deans and directors, 1993. (Box 22)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - General Professional Advisory Committee, 1990. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Business Education Community Certification Program - Survey responses, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1990-1991. (Box 22)
  - Coalition for Access, Affordability and Diversity, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1993. (Box 22)
  - Consolidation of museums, 1992. (Box 22)
  - Governor's Commission on Excellence in Education, 1986-1989. (Box 22)
  - Maps - Private colleges, community colleges and colleges/universities, undated. (Box 22)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Management, 1993-1994. (Box 22)
  - Family Life Education, undated. (Box 22)
  - General correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 22)
  - General correspondence, 1993 Mar-July. (Box 22)
  - General correspondence, 1993 Aug-Sept. (Box 22)
  - General correspondence, 1993 Oct-Dec. (Box 22)
  - General correspondence, 1994 Jan. (Box 22)
  - VCU / MCV, 1989-1990. (Box 23)
  - VCU / MCV Teaching Hospital, 1989-1991. (Box 23)
  - VCU / MCV Teaching Hospital - Hospital governance, 1989. (Box 23)
  - MCV Steam Plant Replacement Project, 1990-1991. (Box 23)
  - VCU, 1991. (Box 23)